http://www.stainlessandalloy.com/privacy-policy/

Home
All Products
AngleBarBarFlat BarHex BarRound BarSquare BarBollardsBrass NipplesBronze FittingsBronze FittingsBronze 45 Degree ElbowsBronze 90 Degree ElbowsBronze BushingsBronze CapsBronze Countersunk PlugsBronze CouplingsBronze CrossesBronze Hex LocknutsBronze Hex NipplesBronze Reducing 90 ElbowsBronze Reducing Branch TeesBronze Reducing CouplingsBronze Reducing Hex NipplesBronze Square Head Cored PlugsBronze Square Head Solid PlugsBronze Street 45 Degree ElbowsBronze Street 90 Degree ElbowsBronze TeesBronze UnionsButt Weld FittingsButt Weld FittingsButt Weld 45 Degree ElbowsButt Weld 90 Degree ElbowsButt Weld CapsButt Weld Concentric ReducersButt Weld Eccentric ReducersButt Weld Reducing TeesButt Weld Short Radius 90 ElbowsButt Weld TeesCast FittingsCast FittingsCast 45 Degree ElbowsCast 90 Degree ElbowsCast CapsCast CrossesCast Full CouplingsCast Half CouplingsCast Hex BushingsCast Hex PlugsCast Reducing CouplingsCast Square PlugCast Street 90 ElbowsCast TeesCast UnionsElectrical ConduitElectrical ConduitConduitConduit CouplingsConduit ElbowsConduit NipplesFlangesFlangesBlind Plate FlangesLap Joint FlangesRaised Face Blind FlangesRaised Face Slip on FlangesRaised Face Socket Weld FlangesRaised Face Threaded FlangesRaised Face Weld Neck FlangesSlip on Plate FlangesForged FittingsForged FittingsForged 45 Degree ElbowsForged 90 ElbowsForged CapsForged CrossesForged Full CouplingsForged Half CouplingsForged Hex BushingsForged Hex PlugsForged InsertsForged Reducing CouplingsForged Reducing TeesForged Square PlugsForged TeesForged UnionsPipePipeSeamless PipeWelded PipePlate and SheetPlate and SheetPlatePolished SheetSheetPneumatic FittingsPneumatic Fittings1/4 Industrial Interchange Pneumatic Fittings3/8 Industrial Interchange Pneumatic FittingsARO 210 Interchange Pneumatic Fittings Lincoln Interchange Pneumatic FittingsMini Type Quick Disconnect Pneumatic FittingsParker Interchange Pneumatic FittingsST Series High Flow Pneumatic FittingsUniversal Series Pneumatic FittingsPVC FittingsPVC FittingsPVC 45 Degree ElbowsPVC 90 Degree ElbowsPVC AdaptersPVC CapsPVC CouplingsPVC Full CouplingsPVC Hex BushingsPVC PlugsPVC Reducing CouplingsPVC TeesPVC UnionsPVC NipplesSanitary Clamp FittingsSanitary Clamp FittingsSanitary 3 Piece Segmented ClampsSanitary Clamp 180 Degree U BendsSanitary Clamp 45 Degree ElbowsSanitary Clamp 45 Degree LateralsSanitary Clamp 90 Degree ElbowsSanitary Clamp AdaptersSanitary Clamp ASME Tank FerrulesSanitary Clamp ASME Tank Long FerrulesSanitary Clamp Concentric ReducersSanitary Clamp CrossesSanitary Clamp Eccentric ReducersSanitary Clamp Flanged GasketsSanitary Clamp GasketsSanitary Clamp Long FerrulesSanitary Clamp Recessless FerrulesSanitary Clamp Reducing 90 Non-Tapered ElbowsSanitary Clamp Reducing AdaptersSanitary Clamp Reducing Rubber Hose AdaptersSanitary Clamp Reducing TeesSanitary Clamp Rubber Hose AdaptersSanitary Clamp Sch 10 Long FerrulesSanitary Clamp Sch 10 Short FerrulesSanitary Clamp Sch 5 CapsSanitary Clamp Sch 5 ClampsSanitary Clamp Sch 5 GasketsSanitary Clamp Sch 5 Long FerrulesSanitary Clamp Sch 5 Short FerrulesSanitary Clamp Short FerrulesSanitary Clamp Short Reducing FerrulesSanitary Clamp Solid End CapsSanitary Clamp Tank Welding FerrulesSanitary Clamp Tank Welding Long FerrulesSanitary Clamp TeesSanitary Clamp Thermometer CapsSanitary Clamp True YSanitary Clamp Tygon Hose AdaptersSanitary Double Hinged Heavy Duty ClampsSanitary Double Hinged Heavy Duty Wing Nut ClampsSanitary Heavy Duty ClampsSanitary Heavy Duty Wing Nut ClampsSanitary High Pressure ClampsSanitary Hinged Clamps Light DutySanitary TubeSanitary ValvesSanitary ValvesSanitary 2-Way Ball ValvesSanitary 3-Way Ball ValvesSanitary Ball Check ValvesSanitary Butterfly ValvesSanitary Spring Check ValvesSanitary Weld FittingsSanitary Weld FittingsSanitary Weld 180 Degree U BendsSanitary Weld 45 Degree ElbowsSanitary Weld 45 Degree Laterals Sanitary Weld 45 Degree Reducing LateralsSanitary Weld 45 Degree Short ElbowsSanitary Weld 90 Degree ElbowsSanitary Weld 90 Degree Short ElbowsSanitary Weld CapsSanitary Weld Concentric ReducersSanitary Weld CrossesSanitary Weld Eccentric ReducersSanitary Weld Reducing Short Outlet TeesSanitary Weld Reducing Tees PageSanitary Weld Short Outlet TeesSanitary Weld Tees PageSanitary Weld True YSanitary Weld Tube x Pipe Sch 10 AdaptersSanitary Weld Tube x Pipe Sch 40 AdaptersSanitary Weld Tube x Pipe Sch 5 AdaptersSanitary Weld Type A Stub EndsStainless NipplesStainless NipplesExtra Heavy NipplesHex NipplesKing NipplesStandard NipplesSteel NipplesSteel NipplesNipplesSeamless NipplesStructuralStructuralBeamChannelTubeTubeRectangular TubeSeamless TubeSquare TubeWelded TubeValvesWeapon Silencers
About
Services
Fabrication
Resources
Contact
Login
Cart
Item Added:
Test
Qty:
Contact Us for Project Bids
(800) 282-9694
Products
Angle
Bar
Flat Bar
Hex Bar
Round Bar
Contact
0 Item(s)
Test
Test
Qty:
Total: $0.00
View Cart
Login
Login
Email Address
Password
New Customer?
Start Here
Forgot Password?
Reset Password
Home
>
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy of stainlessandalloy.com
Types of Data Collected
Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Usage Data. Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application. Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by the Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User. Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services. The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through this Application and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Data Controller of all responsibility.
Mode and Place of Processing the Data
Method of Processing
The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data.
Access to the Data may be available to Data Processors such as employees involved with the processing or to external parties providing services to the Data Controller, third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communication agencies. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time.
Place
The Data is processed at the Data Controller headquarters, unless stated otherwise in the rest of this document.
Conservation Time
The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request the Data Controller for their suspension or removal.
The Use of the Collected Data
The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Application to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Contacting the User. The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.
Detailed Information on the Processing of Personal Data
Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Contacting the User
Mailing List or Newsletter Signup Form (This Application)
By registering to the mailing list or to the newsletter, the User's email address may be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning this Application. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to this Application or after performing a purchase. Personal Data collected: Usage Data.
Additional Information About Data Collection and Processing
Legal Action
The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services.
Additional Information About User's Personal Data
In addition to the information in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data.
System Logs and Maintenance
For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).
Data Controller and Owner
Stainless & Alloy Piping
922 Mountain Industrial Drive
Marietta, GA 30060
(800) 282-9694
sales@shawstainless.com
Information Not Contained in This Policy
More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time at its contact information.
The Rights of Users
Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.
Information About This Privacy Policy
The Data Controller is responsible for this privacy policy, prepared starting from the modules provided by Iubenda and hosted on the Iubenda's servers.
Definitions and Legal References
Personal Data (or Data)
Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.
Usage Data
Information collected automatically from this Application (or third party services employed in this Application ), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.
User
The individual using this Application, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refer.
Data Subject
The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers to.
Data Processor
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.
Data Controller (or Application Owner, or Owner)
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing ofPersonal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application.
This Application
The hardware or software tool by which the User Personal Data is collected.
MISSION STATEMENT
Achieve consistent and controlled growth, and thrive with our vendors and customers.
ID Codes
DUNS:
NAICS:
SIC:
096629928
423510
5051
FSC:
NGIP:
9510, 9515, 9520, 4710
57007, 57024, 57025, 57054, 57064, 57084, 57090,
65877, 65894, 65924, 65933, 65927, 65936, 65940,
© Copyright 2020 Shaw Stainless & Alloy. All Rights Reserved.
Item Added
Loading Product.
Part#:
Size:
Flange
Description:
Flange
Pressure:
Flange
Tube OD:
Flange
Sheet Size:
Flange
Run:
Flange
Gauge:
Flange
Grade:
Flange
Qty:
Flange
EA:
EA:
View Cart
Continue Shopping
*Sales tax may apply.
